thumbpress.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy | ThumbPress

**Thumb Press Privacy Policy**  
The following privacy statement covers the Thumb Press Website. Please read this statement regarding our websites. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://thumbpress.com/contact/).

**Privacy**

Your privacy on the internet is important to us. As a part of the operation of ThumbPress.com we gather only email addresses submitted to us, these are used only by ourselves to inform you of any updates or for communication etc and are never passed to any third party for any reason.

The foregoing policy is effective as of January 2009, and ThumbPress.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. This statement and policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Copyright**

All images on ThumbPress.com are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)

**Claims of Infringement**

If you believe that any content appearing on ThumbPress.com infringes on your copyright, [please let us know](http://thumbpress.com/contact/).  
Email us following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.

(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf

Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.
